菲比  明晚我要跟我爸一起吃饭
Hey, Pheebs. I'm having dinner with my dad tomorrow night.
你要来吗
Do you wanna come?
好啊  他挺性感的
Sure, yeah. He's kind of sexy.
不  我也会去
Oh, no, I'll be there too.
行  那么我们得想个暗号
Okay. So we'll come up with some kind of signal.
如果一切进行顺利  你可以离开
If it's going well, you can take off.
不  我是要你过去陪我
No, I just need you there for support.
我还没有告诉他我怀孕了
I haven't told him that I'm pregnant yet.
为什么
Oh. Why not?
因为我知道他会气炸了
Because I know he's gonna flip out,
我讨厌他生气的样子
and I hate it when he's angry.
瑞秋  这跟《爸爸别说教》如出一辙
Rachel, this is all so "Papa Don't Preach."
不  菲比  等一下  他非常严厉
No, Phoebe, wait. He's a scary guy.
有次他抓到我抽烟
I mean, one time he caught me smoking.
他说如果他再看到我抽烟
He said if he ever saw me doing that again,
他就逼我把一整包烟吃掉
he'd make me eat the entire pack.
那我一定得去
Wow. Well, I will be there.
天啊  我不会让那个男人逼你把宝宝吃掉
Gosh, I'm not gonna let that man make you eat your baby!
那个家伙是谁  我想我认识他
Hey, who is that guy? I think I know him.
-才怪  -你怎么会认识
- No, you don't. - No, you don't.
天啊
Oh, my God!
莫妮卡  他是你单身女郎派对上的脱衣舞男
Monica, he's the stripper from your bachelorette party!
什么
Her what?
你的秘密单身女郎派对
Your secret bachelorette party.
你办了单身女郎派对
You had a bachelorette party?
她用牙解开了他的丁字裤
She untied his G-string with her teeth.
谁快让我住嘴
Somebody stop me!
我们不是说好不办单身汉或单身女郎派对吗
I thought we weren't having bachelor, bachelorette parties.
我们都觉得这个传统很愚蠢
We agreed that it's a silly tradition.
那个传统棒极了
It's a grand tradition!
抱歉  她们给了我一个大惊喜
I'm sorry. They surprised me.
我真的没有办法
There was nothing I could do.
你可以用手解嘛
Well, you could've untied it with your hands.
这太不公平了
This is so unfair.
我非常想帮我最好的朋友办单身汉派对
The one thing I wanted was to throw my best friend a bachelor party...
却不能那么做
...but I wasn't allowed to.
我们只能一起去吃牛排
All we got was a stupid steak dinner.
女服务生跟你回家睡了
You went home with the waitress.
对  那一晚真的很美妙
Yeah, that was a pretty good night.
我不敢相信你没有告诉我
I can't believe you didn't tell me.
你知道婚姻的两大支柱
You know that the two pillars of marriage
是公开跟诚实
are openness and honesty.
我就知道送你那本书
I knew giving you that book
总有一天我自己会遭报应
was gonna come back and bite me in the ass.
我帮大家点摩洛哥鸡肉怎么样
How about I order everyone the Moroccan chicken?
我不吃肉
Oh, I don't eat meat.
那是鸡肉
It's chicken!
那个我也不吃
I don't eat that either.
我一直都搞不懂你们女同志
I never understand you lesbians.
宝贝  告诉我  你最近怎么样
So, baby, tell me, what's new with you?
事实上...
Well, actually...
您的74年拉费红酒  先生
Your '74 Lafite, sir.
74年
'74?
我点的是75年的  那一年的酒味道醇美
I ordered the '75. That's a magnificent wine.
74年的酒烂透了
The '74 is sewage!
你为什么要给我上那么烂的酒
Why would you bring me sewage?
这个问题很难吗
Is that a hard question?
你是白痴吗  所以你才会来当服务生
Are you an idiot? Is that why you're a waiter?
这就是我告诉经理今晚不想为你服务的原因
This is why I told the manager i wouldn't wait on you tonight.
少来了  别那么幼稚
Oh, come on. Don't be such a baby.
你应该注意到了他真的很吓人
In case you didn't notice, that is a scary man.
但他说得对  74年的酒真的很难喝
He's right, though. The '74 is absolute piss.
这是个天大的错误  菲比
This was such a huge mistake.
我不敢告诉他  菲比  我做不到
I can't tell him, Phoebe. I can't. I can't. I can't.
-瑞秋...  -没事  这样吧
- Rachel... - No, it's okay. This is what's gonna happen.
我再等上几年
I'm gonna wait a couple of years,
然后宝宝会告诉他
and then the baby will tell him.
怎么  让他拿宝宝撒气吗
Why? So he can get mad at the baby?
那就是宝宝要解决的问题了
Hey, that is the baby's problem.
服务生没问题吧
Everything okay with the waiter?
我不知道  我去了洗手间
I have no idea. I went to the bathroom.
甜心  你刚才准备告诉我你的近况
So, sweetie, you were starting to tell me what is new with you.
我有了
I got TiVo.
-什么是有了  -就是怀孕的意思
- What's TiVo? - It's slang for "pregnant."
菲比
Phoebe.
你真的怀孕了吗
Are you really pregnant?
对也不对
Well, yes and no.
但"不对"是不对的答案
Except, not no.
总而言之  对
So to sum it up, yeah.
孩子的爸爸是谁
Who is the father?
不  拜托  别告诉就是她
Oh, no. Please don't tell me it's her.
不  是罗斯  你喜欢罗斯
No, it's Ross. It's Ross. You like Ross.
爸爸  我希望你能接受这件事
Daddy, I hope you're okay with all of this.
想一想  这是件好事
Think about it. This is a good thing.
这是你第一个外孙
This is your first grandchild!
你要当外公了
You're gonna be a poppy!
没错  我要当外公了
That's true. I'm a poppy!
我要当外公了
I'm gonna be a poppy!
-婚礼什么时候举行  -谁的婚礼
- So when is the wedding? - The who?
婚礼  你们得举行婚礼
The wedding. There's going to be a wedding.
小姑娘  你休想坐在那里告诉我
Young lady, don't you sit there and tell me
我的第一个外孙会是个私生子
my first grandchild is gonna be a bastard!
瑞秋·凯伦·格林  告诉我你们会举行婚礼
Rachel Karen Green, tell me there is gonna be a wedding!
二月二日举行
February 2nd!
今天去看你上课感觉很棒
It was really cool seeing you lecture today.
谢谢  虽然我觉得你看起来
Thanks. Although it kind of seemed like
像是睡着了
you were falling asleep there a little.
不  我闭上眼睛
No, no, I had my eyes closed
是为了专心听讲  好好消化吸收
so I could concentrate and, you know, take it all in.
我很多学生都会那么做
Yeah, a lot of my students do that.
-我得走了  -今晚见
- I've got to get going. - Okay, I'll see you tonight?
-好  -再见
- Yeah, okay. - Bye.
谢谢你让我参观你收集的半宝石
Thanks for showing me your semiprecious-stone collection.
真的很棒
It's amazing.
天啊  你的床上功夫一定很厉害
My God, you must be good in bed.
你跟蒙娜交往了一阵子  情况如何
So you and Mona, it's been a while now. How's it going?
很不错
It's good. It's going good.
我们处得很好  她很...
I mean, we get along great. She's so...
-辣  -我本来说很温柔  但你答对了
- Hot? - I was gonna say sweet, but yeah!
她能接受瑞秋和宝宝的事吗
She's okay with Rachel and the baby?
我还没有告诉她
I haven't actually told her yet.
我不想吓跑她
I don't wanna scare her off, you know?
你得老实说
You have to be honest with her.
不然的话  你以为你们的方向一致
Otherwise, you may think you're going down the same path...
事实上你们走上了不同的道路
...but you're really going down different ones.
我要把那本书抢过来  拿它把你打死
I'm gonna take that book and I'm gonna beat you to death with it.
天啊  你一定会爱死我的
Oh, my God, you are gonna love me so much.
关于单身女郎派对的事  我真的很过意不去
I felt bad about the bachelorette party thing...
所以今晚你要办单身汉派对
...so tonight you're gonna have a bachelor party.
什么
What?
我在餐厅的同事给了我一个电话号码
I got this number from this guy at work
我雇了一个脱衣舞娘来跳舞给你看
and I hired a stripper to come dance for you.
我可以进太太名人堂了吧
Am I going in the wife hall of fame or what?
亲爱的  这太疯狂了  我不要脱衣舞娘
Honey, that's crazy. I don't want a stripper.
你能让她说完吗
Will you let the lady talk?
来吧  一定会很好玩的
Come on, it'll be fun.
这样会让我觉得好过一点
It'll make me feel so much better.
听着  我很感激  但这样有点奇怪
Look, I appreciate it, but it's a little creepy.
我已经不是单身汉了
I'm not a bachelor anymore.
别把它当成是单身汉派对
Don't think of it as a bachelor party.
把它当成是结婚两个月的礼物
Think of it as a two-month anniversary present.
当然  结婚一年是纸婚
Sure. One year is paper,
两个月的话可以看艳舞
but two months is lap dance.
拜托  我觉得好过意不去
Please, I feel so bad.
就去看看那个辣妹脱光衣服吧
Just watch the hot woman get naked!
-好吧  但我这么做是为了你  -太帅了
- Fine, but I'm only doing this for you. - Yeah!
还有乔伊
And Joey.
谢谢  你还想邀请谁
Thank you. Who else do you wanna invite?
光罗斯跟乔伊就够丢脸了
No, no, no. Just Ross and Joey is embarrassing enough.
抱歉  我没办法去  今晚我跟蒙娜有约
Actually, sorry, I can't even make it. I'm seeing Mona tonight.
谁会为了假单身汉派对
I understand: who would cancel an actual date
取消真正的约会
just to go to a fake bachelor party?
抱歉  我得取消今晚的约会  宝贝
I'm sorry. I gotta cancel tonight, baby.
抱歉我无法参加你想像出来的婚礼
I'm sorry I won't make it to your imaginary wedding,
那天我很忙
but I'm busy that day.
我得参加独角兽受洗礼跟小精灵的戒酒会
I already have a unicorn baptism and a leprechaun bar mitzvah.
我知道  我乱了方寸
I know, I know. I panicked. I panicked.
我不想让他对着我大叫
I didn't want him to start yelling at me
把我当成74年拉图红酒
like I was some '74 Latour.
是拉费
It's Lafite.
74年拉图红酒喝起来真的很不错
The '74 Latour is actually drinking quite nicely.
好吧  他来了  我得告诉他  我会很坚强
All right, here he comes. I'm gonna tell him. I'm gonna be strong.
我刚刚给一个朋友打了电话
I just called a friend of mine.
我应该我可以在这么短的时间内
I think I may be able to book The Plaza
订到广场饭店
on short notice.
真的吗
Really?
广场饭店
The Plaza?
爸爸
Oh, Daddy!
爸爸  我得跟你谈一谈  请坐
Right. Daddy, I need to talk to you. Please sit down.
什么事  宝贝
What is it, sweetie?
我们不会举行婚礼
There's not gonna be a wedding.
-罗斯跟我不会结婚  -什么
- Ross and I aren't getting married. - What?
-对不起  爸爸  -我不敢相信
- I'm sorry, Daddy. - I don't believe this!
爸爸  请保持冷静
Daddy, stay calm, please.
保持冷静  你叫我怎么保持冷静
Stay calm? How do you expect me to stay calm?
我完全无法接受  瑞秋  我要知道为什么
This is unacceptable, Rachel. And I wanna know why!
因为那个混蛋不愿意娶你吗
Is it because that punk Ross won't marry you?
-是那样吗  -对  他说我是瑕疵品
- That's it. Is that it? - Yes. He says I'm damaged goods.
快结婚了  你很紧张吧
So, you nervous about getting married?
你这是搞什么名堂
What are you doing?
我们假装这是你结婚前的单身汉派对
Let's pretend it's a real bachelor party, before your wedding.
那样比较好玩
It'll be more fun.
好吧  我不敢相信明天是我的大喜之日
All right. I can't believe tomorrow's the big day.
知道你再也没法跟别的女人在一起
How's it feel knowing you're never gonna
你有什么感觉
be with another woman again?
知道你每天醒过来都会看到同一张脸
Knowing you're gonna have to wake up to the same face every day...
直到死神来拯救你
...until you finally have the sweet release of death.
你说得对  这样比较好玩
You're right. This is more fun.
她来了  快点
That's her! Okay, come on!
哪个幸运儿是钱德勒
Which one of you lucky boys is Chandler?
是我
That's me!
That's me.
乔伊·崔比安尼  你的头号仰慕者
Joey Tribbiani. Big fan.
-那是卧室吗  -对  就在那边
- Is that a bedroom? - Yeah, right over there.
好吧  你准备好就进来
All right. Whenever you're ready.
那好奇怪
That was weird.
-她为什么要到卧室去  -我等着呢
- Why would she go in the bedroom? - I'm waiting.
-她是...  -她是脱光衣服的妓女
- So she's a... - Yeah, that's one naked hooker.
我喜欢你家  这玩意从哪里来的
I love your place. Where is this guy from?
那是在加尔各答买的18世纪印度工艺品
That's an 18th-century Indian artifact from Calcutta.
原来你不只喜欢研究恐龙
So you're more than just dinosaurs.
我涉猎很广的
So much more.
天啊  我很抱歉
Oh, my God! I am so sorry!
算了  那是在一号码头商店买的
Forget it. It's from Pier 1.
抱歉
Sorry.
你以为你可以搞大我女儿的肚子
You think you can knock up my daughter
然后不娶她吗
and then not marry her?
我要杀了你
I'm gonna kill you!
事实上  我现在真的很不方便
You know, this is actually not a great time for me.
快解释给我听  盖勒
So come on. Explain yourself, Geller.
你先让我的瑞秋怀孕
First, you get my Rachel pregnant.
你让瑞秋怀孕了
You got Rachel pregnant?
-谁干的  -就是你
- Who did? - You did!
是的
Yes.
没错  但那是一夜情  那毫无意义
Yes, I did, but it was a one-night thing. It meant nothing.
真的吗  我女儿对你来说毫无意义
Oh? Really? That's what my daughter means to you, nothing?
不是的  她对我来说意义重大
No, sir. She means a lot to me.
我在乎...我爱瑞秋
I care... I love Rachel.
-什么  -但不是那种爱
- What? - But not that way.
我没有爱上她  我把她当成朋友
I'm not in love with her. I love her like a friend.
你就是那样对待朋友的吗
Really? That's how you treat a friend,
你搞大她的肚子又不肯娶她
you get her in trouble and refuse to marry her?
我有跟她求婚  但我不是真心的
Hey, I offered to marry her. But I didn't want to.
为什么  因为你想跟这个荡妇鬼混
Well, why not? So you could spend your time with this tramp?
荡妇
Tramp?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
格林医生  蒙娜  蒙娜  格林医生
Dr. Green, Mona. Mona, Dr. Green.
我不敢相信里面有个脱光衣服的妓女
I can't believe there is a naked hooker in there!
或许她是妓女兼脱衣舞娘...
Wait, wait. Maybe she's a hooker and a stripper...
但她会搞不清楚该做什么
...but she got confused about what's she supposed to do.
有可能  技术上来说她确实脱光了衣服
Could be. I mean, technically, she did strip.
只是我们错过了
We just missed it.
小姐
Ma'am?
你也是脱衣舞娘吗
Are you also a stripper?
不是  但我可以假装  那得另外收钱
No, but I can pretend to strip. But that's gonna cost extra.
这是另外收钱的项目  手拷  鞭打...
Okay, here's the extras: Handcuffs, spanking...
或许莫妮卡是在跟你开玩笑
Maybe Monica's playing a joke on you.
帮自己老公找妓女  那真的很好笑
You know? Getting her own husband a hooker. That's pretty funny.
是很好笑  或许我生日的时候她会去杀人
That is funny. Maybe for my birthday she'll murder someone.
我敢说罗斯也知情
I'll bet Ross was in on it too.
他"刚好"很忙
I mean, he was "conveniently" busy.
你不介意我抽烟吧
Do you mind if I smoke in here?
你还是不要...
Actually, I'd rather...
抽吧  反正我们也会烧掉那个房间
Yeah, go ahead. We're gonna have to burn that room down anyway.
你为什么一直没有告诉我
How could you have kept all this from me?
我打算告诉你  但是...
I was going to tell you, but...
但是什么  你以为你可以得到你要的
But what? You figure you'd get what you wanted,
然后像甩了瑞秋一样甩掉她
then you'd dump her like you did Rachel.
我没有甩掉瑞秋  我们也没有在一起
Hey, I did not dump Rachel. Nor are we still together.
我可以...
Can I...?
让答录机接吧
Why don't we just let the machine get that.
罗斯  我是乔伊  这里有个妓女
Hey, Ross, it's Joey. There's a hooker over here...
我们想或许你知情
...and we thought maybe you'd know something about it.
不
No! No! No!
不  我需要躺一下
No! I need to lie down.
今晚是单身汉派对之夜
So, tonight's the night of the big bachelor party?
对  谢谢你给我那个女孩的电话号码
Yeah. Thanks for giving me that girl's number.
别客气  这是给谁办的派对
No problem. Say, who's the party for?
-我老公  -你帮你老公雇了一个妓女
- For my husband. - You hired your husband a hooker?
-她是脱衣舞娘  -不  她是妓女
- She's a stripper. - No, she's a hooker.
他们有时也这样称呼脱衣舞娘吗
Is that what they call strippers sometimes?
因为她们本身就是妓女
When they're hookers.
天啊  史都  我不敢相信你会这么做
Oh, my God. Stu, I can't believe you did this.
你确定她是妓女吗
Now, you're absolutely sure she's a hooker?
如果不是的话  那她就是我约过
It's either that, or she's just the best,
技术最好  价钱最贵的女孩
most expensive date I ever had.
或许她是故意帮你雇了个妓女
Maybe she meant to get you a hooker.
她为什么要那么做
Why would she do that?
或许她要你好好学一学
Maybe she wants you to learn something.
你在床上有表现不好的方面吗
Is there anything you're really bad at, you know, sexually?
这个单身汉派对简直烂到家了
This is the worst bachelor party ever.
-你们怎么那么久  -再过一分钟就好
- What's taking you boys so long? - In a minute!
"一分钟"  一分钟内会发生什么事
"In a minute"? What's gonna happen in a minute?
好吧  或许你该去请她离开
All right. Maybe you should ask her to leave.
-为什么是我  -这是你的单身汉派对
- Why me? - Hey, it's your bachelor party.
所以应该是你去说
Which is why you should do it.
我不要  你去
I don't want to. You do it.
-你去  -你去
- You do it. - You do it.
好吧  剪刀石头布
All right. Rock, paper, scissors
决定谁去请那个妓女离开
for who has to tell the whore to leave.
怎么了
What?
我想念这种日子
I miss this.
我觉得我们以前根本没做过这种事
I don't think we've actually done this before.
不  我想念跟你鬼混的日子
No, I miss hanging out with you.
-我们还是混在一起  -跟以前不一样了
- We still hang out. - Not like we used to.
还记得吗  你跟我我们以前老是黏在一起
Remember? You and me, we used to be inseparable.
现在一切都变得不一样了
You know, now it's like things are different.
的确不一样了  我结婚了
Well, you know, things are different. I'm married now.
别误会我  我为你们感到高兴
And, hey, don't get me wrong, I am so happy for you guys.
我只是想念我们一起鬼混的日子  知道吗
I just miss hanging out. Just us, you know?
我也是
Yeah, I miss that too.
听我说  从现在开始
I'll tell you what. From now on,
我们要找时间一起出去玩
we'll make time to hang out with each other.
没问题  过来
You got it. Come here.
天啊
Oh, God.
听着  我差一点就要洗劫你们了
Listen, I am this close to robbing you guys.
她是妓女  她是...
She's a hooker! She's a hooker! She's a...
嗨  我们通过电话
Hi. We spoke on the phone.
你爸到过我家
So your dad dropped by.
他是个好人
He's a pleasant man.
-不  -我得走了
- Oh, no. - I better go.
我只是走到这里来  我不想错过吵架场面
Just over here. I don't wanna miss the fight.
罗斯  我很抱歉
Ross, I am so sorry.
我发誓明天我会亲自
I promise, I will straighten this out
跟他把事情讲清楚
with him tomorrow, in person.
或是通过电子邮件
Or via e-mail.
我不在乎你爸  我在乎蒙娜
I don't care about your dad. I care about Mona.
当时她在场  都快气疯了
She was there and now she's totally freaked out!
好吧  我也会跟她解释
Okay, I'll fix that too.
-告诉我她的电子邮件信箱  -瑞秋
- What's her e-mail address? - Rachel.
我发誓我会解决的  我发誓我会跟她说
All right, I promise, I'll fix this. I swear. I'll talk to her.
好吧  谢谢你
Okay. Thank you.
就那样  这也算吵架啊
That's it? You call that a fight?
"我们要分手了"  "不  我们没有"
Come on. "We were on a break!" "No, we weren't!"
你们两个这是怎么了
What happened to you two?
谢谢你答应回来
Thank you so much for coming back over.
很好  你也在
Oh, good. You're here.
我还担心今天过来会闹得不痛快
And I was worried that it was going to be uncomfortable.
不  蒙娜  听我说
No, Mona, just hear me out.
首先我很抱歉  我爸对你大叫
First of all, I am so sorry about my father yelling at you.
但我听说你控制住了自己的脾气
But I heard that you held your own.
你得告诉我你是怎么做到的
You have to tell me how you did that.
-说重点  -好吧
- Focus. - Okay.
罗斯跟我以前交往过
Yes, Ross and I used to date.
我们的确有宝宝了
And yes, we are gonna have a baby.
但我们绝对不可能复合
But we are definitely not getting back together.
我怎么能相信你的话
How can I be sure of that?
因为我们把彼此逼疯了
Because we drove each other crazy.
他占有欲很强  爱吃醋
He was possessive, he was jealous.
他从来都放不下那些小事
He could never just let the little things go.
我还要跟这个女人交往呢
Trying to date this woman.
但那都比不上他的温柔体贴
None of that compared to how kind and gentle...
无微不至
...and thoughtful he is.
或许你不该碰我
You probably shouldn't touch me.
我不想介入这么复杂的事
I don't wanna get in the middle of something so complicated.
我明白  但是蒙娜
I get it, but, Mona,
哪段感情不复杂呢
what relationship is not complicated?
我们都有自己的包袱  你也一样
We all have our baggage. You must too.
不然你为什么还是单身呢
Why else would you still be single?
我得走了
I'm so gonna leave right now.
我应该为你把门开着吗
Should I leave this open for you too?
我还不确定  你为什么不告诉我
I'm not sure yet. Why didn't you just tell me about all this?
因为我跟瑞秋之间的事
Because what's going on with Rachel
跟我对你的感觉没有关系
has nothing to do with how I feel about you.
你还是应该告诉我
You still should have told me.
我知道  我打算那么做
I know, and I was going to, but...
但我想最好  还是让瑞秋的爸爸来告诉你
I thought it was better that you heard it from Rachel's father.
我犯了个错误...
I made a mistake...
但那是因为我真的很喜欢你  真的
...but it's only because I really, really like you. Really.
好吧  我想你可以把门关上了
Okay. I guess you can close the door now.
我忘了拿皮包  你们和好了
Forgot my purse. Oh, you guys made up.
他是接吻高手  对吧  我这就闪
He's a good kisser, isn't he? I'm going!
我发誓我不知道她是妓女
I swear I didn't know she was a hooker.
你让她在这里抽烟了吗
Did you let her smoke in here?
你奶奶的被单上还有她的屁股印子
Her ass-print is still on your grandmother's quilt.
你觉得抽烟的事是重点吗
Do you really want to talk about smoking?
你知道吗  我要补偿你
You know what, I'm gonna make this up to you.
我答应要帮你请脱衣舞娘...
I promised you a stripper...
我一定会做到
...and you're gonna get a stripper.
-莫妮卡  等一下  -怎么了
- Monica, wait. - What?
继续
Carry on.
这双网球鞋好紧
These tennis shoes are so tight.
-我想把它们脱掉  -麻烦你别说话
- I think I'll take them off. - Could you not narrate?
知道了  帅哥
Gotcha, sailor.
就因为你不爱那个家伙...
Just because you're not in love with the guy...
-你跟你爸说实话了  -大约一小时前
- You told your dad the truth. - About an hour ago.
-你想去看电影吗  -好
- Wanna go see a movie? - Yes.
再见  爸爸
Bye, Dad.
我无法接受  爱跟结婚有什么关系
It's unacceptable! What the hell does love have to do with it?
还有比爱更重要的事
There are more important things than love.
你得考虑宝宝
You have to think about the baby.
你得想想  你做的决定会有什么后果
You have to think about the consequences of your decisions!
我的确会想我做的决定会有什么后果
Hey, I do think about the consequences of my decisions!
你有什么权利...
Well, what gives you the right to...?
去死吧
Go to hell!
蠢男人敢打我家电话
Stupid guy on my phone.